A Guide to the Governor Henry Lee Executive Papers, 1791-1794
Library of Virginia
County lieutenants including Arthur Campbell, David Shepherd, George Clendenin, John P. Duvall, John Stuart, Thomas Newton, Jr., & Smith Snead communicate with the Governor Lee on various topics. Arthur Campbell, Washington Co., writes extensively on Indian affairs and frontier defense (1792 March 28; 1792 July 19 & 20; 1792 Sept. 10; 1792 Oct. 5, 11, & 17; 1792 Nov. 1, 3, & 12; 1792 Dec. 5; 1793 April 24; 1793 June 24 & 30; 1793 July 6; 1793 Oct. 3; 1794 April 15, 21, & 29; 1794 July 9). In addition, Campbell corresponds on the subject of the act of the General Assembly establishing Walker's line as the boundary between North Carolina & Virginia (1792 June 25), the jurisdiction of William Blount, Governor of the Territory South of the Ohio River (1792 Sept. 4), charges against Capt. Andrew Lewis by Lt. Willoughby of the Washington Militia (1793 Aug. 31; 1793 Oct. 9, 11, & 29; 1794 Jan. 17; 1794 May 8 & 12), and the militia law, insurrection in Pennsylvania, & movements by the Creek Indians (1794 Aug. 21). David Shepherd, Ohio Co., encloses a letter from Henry Knox on the defense of the frontier, as well as a letter from William McMachan regarding Indian attacks (1792 April 14). John Duvall, Harrison Co., writes of murder committed by the Indians in that county & the defeat of Gen. St. Claire (1791 Dec. 8). Shortly thereafter, Duvall communicates in relation to troops raised for the defense of Harrison Co. (1792 Dec. 20). George Clendenin, Kanawha Co., too writes about Indian affairs (1792 May 26; 1792 Dec. 10). In addition, he often discusses Hugh Caperton's militia and the defense of the county (1792 March 8; 1792 Sept. 21 & 22; 1793 Jan. 27, 28, & 31; 1793 March 5; 1793 April 12; 1793 Dec. 16). John Stuart, Greenbrier Co., provides information on a company being raised & commanded by Capt. Caperton for the defense of Greenbrier & Kanawha counties (1792 Feb. 8 & 1792 Aug. 6). He also mentions the appointment of six scouts on the frontier (1794 June 9) and the receipt of ammunition (1794 July 16). Thomas Newton, Jr., Norfolk, writes extensively about the pestilence in the West Indies & the quarantine of vessels (1793 June 16, 22, & 30; 1793 Sept. 23 & 28; 1793 Oct. 1, 5, 13, 15, 19-21, 25, 26 & 30; 1793 Nov. 13-15, 19, & 28; 1794 Aug. 7, 10, & 18; 1794 Sept. 24; 1794 Oct. 4, 15, & 21; 1794 Nov. 9 & 21), the Cape Henry Light House (1792 Jan. 9), a slave insurrection (1792 May 10 & 19), arms & ammunition (1792 June 20; 1793 March 12; 1793 April 29; 1793 Aug. 23; 1794 Oct. 7), Fort Nelson & coastal defense (1793 May 24 & 25; 1793 Aug. 22; 1794 June 10; 1794 Sept. 21), French ships & emigrants (1793 July 9; 1793 Aug. 2; 1794 Sept. 10; 1794 Oct. 15), privateers & the neutrality laws (1793 June 2; 1794 March 19; 1794 Oct. 15; 1794 June 14; 1794 Nov. 28), the Norfolk militia (1794 Feb. 12 & 23; 1794 March 9; 1794 Sept. 10), shots fired from the British ship Daedalus (1793 Feb. 24), the embargo (1794 April 4), and a riot in Norfolk (1794 June 4). Lastly, Smith Snead, Northampton Co., writes concerning ammunition and an attempted slave insurrection (1792 May 5, July 9 & 21).
Andrew Lewis & Hugh Caperton, Captains of Volunteer Militia in the western counties, were appointed to guard Virginia's western frontier. Lewis set out from Richmond on 2 December 1791and frequently corresponds with Governor Lee concerning Indian movements, attacks & depredations (1792 April 27; 1792 June 5; 1792 Aug. 24; 1792 Oct. 3; 1793 April 9; 1793 May 8; 1793 Sept. 12 & 29; 1793 Nov. 3; 1793 Dec. 19 & 24; 1794 Feb. 17; 1794 April 17 & 19), rations (1792 Feb. 7), arms & ammunition (1792 Feb. 6; 1793 Jan. 30), pay (1792 Dec. 22; 1793 Dec. 13 & 23; 1794 Jan. 1), recruiting of troops (1792 Dec. 22; 1794 Feb. 5), the killing of friendly Indians by Capt. Baird (1793 June 26), charges against the Washington Militia & Arthur Campbell (1793 Aug. 17; 1793 Oct. 13; 1793 Nov. 6, 7, 23, & 26; 1793 Dec. 19 & 23; 1794 May 9), volunteers for the suppression of the Whiskey Rebellion (1794 Oct. 3), and the general state of the militia & frontier (1793 Feb. 22 & 25; 1793 March 11; 1793 Nov. 6; 1794 April 4 & 8; 1794 May 9; 1794 Aug. 18).
Hugh Caperton was appointed to the command of a company of volunteer militia to defend Greenbrier & Kanawha counties. On 10 Dec. 1791, Caperton & Daniel Boone write regarding the volunteer militia to be raised in these counties. A statement of scouts for Kanawha County by Boone can also be found in these papers (1791 Undated). Caperton writes concerning rations, arms, & ammunition (1792 Oct. 4 & 30; 1793 Oct. 11), pay (1793 April 20), and the recruiting of troops (1793 Nov. 26). In a letter written with George Clendenin he encloses a list of his company in service in Greenbrier Co. (1792 May 6). Caperton accepts his commission as captain of volunteer militia in a letter dated 15 Nov. 1792. He encloses a pay roll of scouts on 20 April 1793. Col. Charles Cameron, Bath Co., writes about Caperton's arrest & trial before a court-martial (1793 Aug. 30 & 1793 Dec. 31). Caperton writes concerning the charges & court-martial on 25 Feb. 1794. On 2 April and again on 30 Aug. 1794, Caperton requests a rehearing before another court-martial. He also submits a petition on 11 Sept. 1794 for the rehearing at his own expense.
James Madison, Jr., Director of the Lunatic Hospital at Williamsburg, & other members of the Court of Directors, often enclose orders to apply to the Auditor of Public Accounts for warrants (1792 Jan. 4; 1792 March 20; 1792 Aug. 11; 1792 Oct. 13; 1793 Feb. 25; 1793 July 19; 1793 Dec. 13; 1794 May 16). In his letter dated 26 Nov. 1793, Madison declares two vacancies in the Court of Directors by the deaths of Benjamin Harrison & William Pasteur. Lastly, on 1 Nov. 1794, James Ruffin was recommended for a vacancy after the resignation of Joseph Hornsby.
Harry Heth, Agent for the Sale of Public Tobacco, encloses the amount of sales of the balance of tobacco received by him (1791 Dec. 24). Also included is Heth's bond as Agent of the Sinking Fund (1792 March 17). Heth was appointed to take the place of Anthony Singleton whose letter of resignation can be found in this collection (1792 Jan. 5).
William Davies, Commissioner of Virginia for Claims Against the United States, continues his work in settling the Revolutionary claims. He writes the Governor with respect to additional clerks (1792 April 28); the impending completion of his work (1792 Oct. 1); accounts & expenses of his office (1793 Jan. 3; 1793 April 1; 1793 July 1; 1793 Oct. 14); the contract with Messrs. Braxton, Herbert, & Claiborne (1793 Feb. 1); a warrant paid to William Finney (1793 March 20); books & papers to be sent to the state from Philadelphia (1793 May 28; 1793 July 18); his recommendation as sheriff of Mecklenburg Co. (1793 July 22); and the report of the General Board of Commissioners including an account of supplies & services during the late war, extracts from the Council Journal, and extracts of correspondence from Virginia governors to him (1794 Feb. 25). Other correspondence from Davies relates to his appointment as agent for the collection of arrears of taxes (1794 Jan. 12); his commission as agent (1794 March 23); and executions against delinquent sheriffs (1794 March 31; 1794 April 8 & 26).
Governor Randolph corresponds often with John Pendleton, Jr., Auditor of Public Accounts, and Jacquelin Ambler, Treasurer, regarding various financial matters. Pendleton regularly encloses lists of warrants issued by him through the Auditor's Office (1792 Feb. 15; 1792 April 28; 1792 Dec. 31; 1793 Oct. 1; 1793 Nov. 5). Additionally, Pendleton encloses an abstract of the funded debt of the state (1792 June 25), a list of executions returned by sheriffs in several counties (1792 Feb. 27), accounts for sending out notices & executions against public delinquents (1792 April 20), and frontier defense expenses (1793 Feb. 11 & 13). Ambler writes regarding lists of lands purchased for non-payment of taxes (1792 Jan. 11), the amount of transfer tobacco in the Treasury (1792 Feb. 14; 1792 June 20), the state of the Treasury (1792 Feb. 25; 1792 Nov. 28; 1794 Oct. 20), funds for the Potomack Company (1792 Nov. 28), the purchase of public tobacco by Richard Bibb (1792 Dec. 11), certificates from the Sinking Fund for warrants issued to foreign creditors (1793 Jan. 10), the exchange rates of foreign coins by Congress (1793 June 13), additional door, locks, & other expenses for the Treasury (1793 Aug. 27), the claim of the state on account of the Federal buildings (1794 Aug. 28), disbursements & discounts made at the Treasury (1794 Sept. 25), and a warrant to the Court of Directors of the Lunatic Hospital (1794 Nov. 4). On 9 Jan. 1793, Ambler & Pendleton apply to the Governor requesting that Mrs. Pearson remain in the house on the public square (1793. Jan. 9).
Additional significant correspondence includes the following: President George Washington re. property carried away by the British (handwritten copy) (1791 Dec. 7); Edward Telfair, Governor of Georgia, transmitting a resolution to keep the Senate doors open to the public (1792 Jan. 31); William Blount, Governor of the Territory South of the Ohio River, re. aid to troops stationed on Virginia's frontiers (1792 March 6); John Harvie & William Foushee, Directors of the James River Canal re. balance due on shares purchased on public account (1792 May 8); Benjamin R. Morgan, Solicitor of Complaints, to James Innes enclosing a bill of equity from William Grayson & others re. the tract of land known as Indiana (1792 Aug. 11); William Blount re. the boundary between Virginia and his territory at the Watkins' line (1792 Sept. 2); Gen. Anthony Wayne to Maj. William McMachan re. the protection of the frontiers of Ohio Co. (1793 Jan. 5); Henry Lee to James Wood, Lt. Gov., re. a suit against the state (1792 Feb. 7); Henry Lee to Wood re. peace with the Southwest Indians & settlement of claims (1793 Feb. 15); Richard E. Lee, Mayor of Norfolk, enclosing a letter from the British Consul re. interference with the civil authority against U.S. citizens engaged in privateering against the British (1793 May 16); Thomas Mifflin, Governor of Pennsylvania, re. the defense of the frontiers (1793 June 23); Robert Taylor, Mayor of Norfolk, re. distressed emigrants from the West Indies (1793 July 13); John Avery, Jr., Secretary, enclosing the proclamation of John Hancock, Governor of Massachusetts, concerning the complaint of William Marshall against the state (1793 July 21); John Hamilton, British Consul, re. an infringement of the President's neutrality proclamation (1793 Aug. 8 & 29); Joseph Jones re. an intended slave insurrection at Petersburg (1793 Aug. 17); Dennis Ramsay, Mayor of Alexandria, re. quarantine of vessels (1793 Sept. 13); Edward Carrington re. the rent of the room in the Capitol formerly occupied by the Solicitor (1793 Sept. 10); Robert Taylor re. measures to prevent the pestilence in Philadelphia & the West Indies (1793 Sept. 17); Fontaine Maury, Mayor of Fredericksburg, re. the infectious fever brought by trading vessels (1793 Sept. 17 & 22); John Barrett, Mayor of Richmond, re. the spread of the malady from Philadelphia (1793 Sept. 17); John Hamilton re. the French Privateer Republic (1793 Sept. 20 & 27); William Prentis, Mayor of Petersburg, re. two persons escaping from quarantine to Petersburg (1793 Oct. 1); Thomas Mifflin re. the suability of a state (1793 Dec. 19); John Hamilton re. the capture of the British Brigantine Cunningham by a French Privateer in U.S. jurisdiction (1793 Dec. 22); Monsieur P.A. Cherui, Vice-Consul of the France Republic at Alexandria, re. his title papers (1794 Jan. 14); Samuel Huntington, Governor of Connecticut, re. a resolution giving instructions to member in Congress (1794 Jan. 15); Robert Taylor re. relief of French emigrants (1794 Jan. 17 & Feb. 10); Dennis Ramsay re. statements of French emigrants from St. Domingo (1794 Feb. 1); A.J. Dallas, Secretary of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, transmitting a copy of their laws (1794 Feb. 11); William Prentis re. precautions against small pox (1794 March 20); Robert Taylor re. the British ship Daedalus (1794 March 23); John Hamilton re. the capture of the British Schooner Delight & Charles taken by a French ship within neutral limits (1794 May 29); John Marshall re. the arrest of the Ship Unicorn, a supposed privateer (1794 July 23 & 28); David Bradford re. opposition to the Excise Law (1794 Aug. 6); Dabney Minor re. leaks in the Capitol roof (1794 Aug. 7); Tench Coxe, Revenue Commissioner, to H.H. Breckinridge re. the Excise Law and the Whiskey Rebellion (1794 Aug. 8); Tench Coxe to H.H. Breckinridge re. a reported dismemberment of Virginia & Pennsylvania (1794 Aug. 29); Edward Carrington re. military stores and three thousand stand of arms to Winchester for use against the insurgents (1794 Sept. 1 & 16); George Jackson re. the Governor's letter & proclamation relative to the riotous party in Pennsylvania (1794 Sept. 9); Henry Lee to James Wood re. the fighting force of the insurgent counties (1794 Sept. 19); Mr. Oster, French Consul, re. an English Frigate with two French prizes at Hampton (1794 Sept. 25 & Oct. 15); Edward Carrington re. insurgents in Maryland, liberty poles, and the arrival of the Governor (1794 Sept. 24); Thomas Mathews re. arms, supplies, troop movements, quotas, desertions, etc. (1794 Oct. 6 & 12); George French, Mayor of Fredericksburg, re. the nomination of James Allan, Jr., as Superintendent of Quarantine (1794 Oct. 19); Edward Carrington re. provision for the return of the militia now in service (1794 Oct. 18); Henry Lee to James Wood stating that he is unable to return in time for the General Assembly (1794 Oct. 23); and Robert Mitchell, Mayor of Richmond, re. small pox (1794 Nov. 13).
Other noteworthy items include: pay roll of Lt. Bladen Ashby's company of Rangers (1791 Dec. 20); receipt for powder & lead for the use of Daniel Boone's Company (1791 Dec. 22); returns for elections to the House of Representatives (1792 Feb. 20 & 23); pay abstract of scouts belonging to Capt. Hugh Caperton's Company (1793 Jan. 29); election certificates for electors of the Presidential & Vice- Presidential elections (1792 Nov.); a roll of Capt. Hugh Caperton's Company showing residence & place of duty (1792 Undated); roll of John Morris' Company of rangers (1793 Jan. 1); proclamation by Gov. Lee prohibiting hostile incursions against the Indians north of the Ohio River while a treaty takes place at Lower Sandusky (1793 May 13); list of Capt. Hugh Caperton's Company at Fort Lee (1793 May 27); proclamation by Gov. Lee regarding the quarantine of vessels coming from Philadelphia, the Grenades, & Tobago (1793 Sept. 17); list of persons who have taken the oath of fidelity in Fairfax County (1793 Oct. 1); pay roll of the militia on guard over the Public Arsenal at New London (1793 Oct. 19); Petersburg resolutions regarding the malignant disease in Philadelphia (1793 Oct. 3); proclamation by Gov. Lee revoking his previous proclamation to perform quarantines (1793 Nov. 25); proclamation by Gov. Lee regarding an award for the capture of Richard Adams (1793 Dec. 11); pay abstract of militia from Washington Co. under Capt. Andrew Lewis (1793 Dec. 13); applications for agents for the collection of arrears of taxes due by delinquent sheriffs (1793 Dec. & 1794 Jan.); resolutions of the North Carolina Assembly regarding the decision of the Federal judiciary that a state may be sued by an individual (1794 Jan. 4); bonds of individuals appointed as agents for collecting taxes & duties (1794 Feb.); muster roll of a detachment of Cornelius Bogard's Company of Rangers commanded by William Wells (1794 March 15); resolution of Congress for an embargo on all ships in U.S. ports for thirty days (1794 March 26); return of laborers employed at Fort Nelson & Fort Norfolk (1794 June 27); rough general orders & division orders to militia (1794 June 30); proclamation by Lt. Gov. Wood regarding a contagious disease in the West Indies and performing quarantines (1794 Aug. 2); report of Maj. G.K. Taylor regarding the taking possession of Capt. Sinclair's ship The Unicorn suspecting of equipping for the purpose of privateering (1794 Aug. 4); proclamation by Gov. Lee regarding banditti from Western Pennsylvania in Virginia (1794 Aug. 19); estimate by Edward Carrington concerning the march of the militia for the suppression of the Whiskey Insurrection (1794 Sept. 4); and a proclamation by Lt. Gov. Wood revoking his proclamation for quarantines (1794 Nov. 4).
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically by date of document with undated items arranged to the rear.
Contents List
- Henry Lee Executive Papers, 1791-1794
- 1791
  - December
    - 2-10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 12-20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 22-24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1792
  - January
    - 3-10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 11-19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 21-31 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - February
    - 1-8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 21-31 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - March
    - 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 12-20 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 21-31 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - April
    - 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 21-30 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - May
    - 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 22-31 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - June
    - 1-9 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 21-30 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - July
    - 2-10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 11-19 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 21-26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - August
    - 2-8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 11-19 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 21-31 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - September
    - 2-10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 12-20 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 21-31 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - October
    - 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 11-20 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 22-31 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - November
    - 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 11-20 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 21-30 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Presidential & Vice Presidential Electors (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - December
    - 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 22-31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pardons
    - A-I (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - J-Y (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 1793
  - January
    - 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 22-31 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - February
    - 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 21-28 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - March
    - 2-8 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 21-30 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - April
    - 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 22-30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - May
    - 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 21-31 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - June
    - 1-8 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 12-16 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 22-30 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - July
    - 2-9 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 21-31 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - August
    - 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 12-20 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 21-31 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - September
    - 2-10 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - October
    - 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - November
    - 2-10 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 12-20 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 21-29 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - December
    - 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 1794
  - January
    - 1-10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 21-31 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - February
    - 1-10 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 11-20 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 21-28 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - March
    - 3-10 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 11-20 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 21-31 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - April
    - 1-10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 11-19 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 21-29 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - May
    - 2-10 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 12-20 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 21-31 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - June
    - 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 22-30 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - July
    - 2-10 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - August
    - 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 21-31 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - September
    - 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 11-19 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - October
    - 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 12-20 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 21-30 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - November
    - 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 12-20 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 21-30 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Point of Fork Arsenal
  - Accounts, Receipts, etc., 1792-1794 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1792-1794 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Pay Rolls (See Oversized), 1792-1793 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Quarterly Accounts of Cash (See Oversized), 1792-1793 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Returns of Ordnance, etc. (See Oversized), 1792-1794 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Oversized (Clamshell Box)
  - 1791
    - Dec. 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Dec. 6 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1792
    - Jan. 31 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Jan. 31 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Feb. 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - March 17 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - May 6 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - June 8 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - June 17 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - July 6 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Aug. 2 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Sept. 5 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Oct. 18 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Oct. 23 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Oct. 30 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Nov. 3 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Nov. 24 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Nov. 28 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Nov. - Presidential Electors (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Pardons - Anderson, Richard C. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Pardons - Joe & Allen (Slaves) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Pardons - Will (Slave) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 1793
    - Jan. 18 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Jan. 30 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Feb. 13 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Feb. 18 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - March 8 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - April 19 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - April 20 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - May 23 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - June 23 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - July 3 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - July 4 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - July 9 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - July 11 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Aug. 16 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Aug. 16 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Sept. 5 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Oct. 13 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Nov. 6 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Nov. 6 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Nov. 29 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Dec. 11 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Dec. 19 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - 1794
    - Jan. 3 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Feb. 1 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Feb. 11 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Feb. 25 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - March 11 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - March 18 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - March 25 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - April 10 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - May 16 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - May 19 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - May 21 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - May 31 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - May 31 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - June 2 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - July 6 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Aug. 16 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Aug. 20 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Sept. 12 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Oct. 18 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Nov. 2 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Nov. 20 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Point of Fork Arsenal
    - Pay Rolls, 1792-1793 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Quarterly Accounts of Cash, 1792-1793 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1791
    - Dec. 20 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1792
    - Feb. 27 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - March 12 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - March 24 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - April 20 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - May 8 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - June 30 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - July [N.D.] (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Dec. 23 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Pardons - Crane, John (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1793